一旦你安装好Android Studio，打开它
Once you install Android Studio you can open it and check for
在运行之前检查有没有升级内容
updates before proceeding.
看上去我们的版本是最新的
Looks like we have the latest version installed already, so
所以我们关闭这个对话框
we can close this dialog.
我们准备用Android Studio 1.01版新建一个项目
We're going to be setting up a new project using Android Studio version 1.01.
如果你发现你的版本和我的看上去不太一样
As you follow along, if things look differently on your computer, that's okay.
可能是你的Android Studio版本更新，没什么大问题
It's probably because you're on a newer version of Android Studio.
遇到任何问题请查看下面的笔记
For the most up-to-date instructions on how to get started,
它会实时更新
you can always check the instructor notes below.
现在，点击这里来新建一个Android Studio项目
Now, let's click here to start a new Android Studio project.
在项目引导页面，我们设置App的名字为Sunshine
In the project wizard, we set the app name to be Sunshine.
然后我们需要定义一个相符的包名
Then we provide a corresponding package name.
包名在所有能在Android上安装的包这个范围内都应该是独一无二的，
The package name should be globally unique across all packages installed
on Android.
为了避免包名冲突
To avoid conflicts,
将你拥有的互联网域名反过来
use the reverse of the name of the internet domain that you own.
这和Java包名的命名惯例相同
This follows the Java package name conventions.
我们用example作为Sunshine App的包名
We're using the combat example name space for
因为它足够坚定
our Sunshine app because it's a sample.
但是你不能将这样包名的App发布到Google Play上去
But you cannot publish an app on Google Play with that name space.
通常就让它保持默认包名
Usually leaving the default package name is fine.
不过，这个课程用的是老版本Android Studio
However, this course was originally filmed with a older version of
默认包括模块名
Android Studio where the module name app was included by default.
所以我们在这里修改下包名
So, we'll edit the package name here, so
这样就和我们用老版本Android Studio创建的目录相符合了
it matches what we had in the older version of Android Studio.
你们也应该加上“.app”
For your code to match the rest of the code in this course,
这样就能和其他代码相配
you should add the dot app as well.
下一步，我们选择项目目录，然后点击Next
Next, we choose our project location and then we can hit Next.
现在我们需要选择最小SDK版本
Now we need to choose our minimum SDK version.
在之前版本的Android Studio
In previous versions of Android Studio,
你还要选择一个目标SDK
you would also have to select the target SDK.
现在的话，项目引导自动设置目标SDK
Now the project wizard automatically sets the target SDK
为最新版本的Android
to the latest version of Android.
不过了解到最小SDK和目标SDK的差别仍然很重要
Even though it's already selected for
即使已经为你选好了
you, it's important to know the distinction between minimum and target SDK.